instafreebie.com 2019-03-30

# Prolific Works - free ebook giveaways

__ Back to About

## Privacy Policy

This document was last updated on October 1, 2018 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Libboo, Inc. (" **Libboo** ", " **we** ", " **our** "" or " **us** ") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a " **User** ") of the Prolific Works website located at https://www.prolificworks.com/ (" **Website** ""), the Prolific Works mobile applications a User downloads (" **Application** ", the Website and Application collectively referred to as the " **Site** ""), the tools and interactive forums made available through the Site and the Prolific Works content sharing platform, in e-mails, texts and other electronic messages between User and the Site, as well as a number of related services (collectively the " **Services** "). This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by: (i) us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by us or any third party; or (ii) any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Site. 

###  Personal information 

We collect several types of information from and about Users including, but not limited to, information: (i) by which you may be personally identified, directly or indirectly, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (" **Personal Information** "), (ii) that is about you but individually does not identify you, and/or (iii) about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Site, the version of the Application you use to access our Site, your location and usage details. 

We collect your information in a variety of ways, including: 

  1. directly from you when you provide it to us
  2. automatically as you navigate through the Site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies and
  3. from third parties.

We may collect Personal Information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, and Services. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect Personal Information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply Personal Information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

###  Non-personal information 

We may collect non-personal information about Users whenever they interact with our Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, and Services. Non-personal information may include, but not limited to, the browser name, the type of computer, telephone and technical information about Users' means of connection to our Site and Services, such as the operating system, internet connection, IP address, browser type, details of your visits to our Site, including traffic data, location data and other resources that you access and use on the Site, and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

###  Web browser cookies 

Our Site may use "cookies" and/or web beacons to enhance User experience. A User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. A User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site and Prolific Works content sharing platform may not function properly. 

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Site are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your Personal Information or they may collect information, including Personal Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. 

###  How we use collected information 

Prolific Works may collect and use Users' Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * _To present and improve our Site_

We may use feedback a User provides to improve our products and services. 

  * _To send periodic emails_

We may use the email address to respond to User inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. 

  * _To process Site registration_

We may use Personal Information of Users for registration with the Site including verifying that an e-mail address is active and valid. 

  * _To provide information or services_

We may use Personal Information to offer a User information or services that they have requested or agreed to receive. 

  * _To provide you with notices about your account_

  * _To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered between you and us_

  * _To use for internal business purposes_

We may use Personal Information for the internal use of the business. 

  * _To use for purposes disclosed_

We may use Personal Information for the purposes disclosed on the Site or with User consent or for any other purpose unrelated to the Site with your consent. 

Additionally, we may send notifications (e.g. in the form of e-mails), and otherwise communicate with a User about services, products, promotions, contests, companies, and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might be of interest. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

###  Canceling your account 

You always have the option to cancel your account with us at any time. You may request to have your registration account information removed by submitting a request to [support@prolificworks.com](mailto:support@prolificworks.com). We will act on your request as promptly as possible and without undue delay. 

###  How we protect your information 

We take reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include firewalls and encryption, internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems. 

We restrict access to Personal Information to Prolific Works employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information to operate, develop or improve our Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, and Services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations. However, we are unable to guarantee that the security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that your information will remain secure under all circumstances. 

Our Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, and Services process information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected. 

###  Minors 

We do not knowingly collect or maintain Personal Information from individuals who are under 13 years of age, and no part of our Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform or Services are designed or intended to attract people under the age of 13. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Site on or through any of its features/registration, make any purchases through the Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we obtain knowledge that a user is under the age of 13, we will take steps to remove that user's Personal Information from our databases. If you believe we might have information from or about a User under 13, please contact us at [support@prolificworks.com](mailto:support@prolificworks.com). 

###  International users 

The Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, and Services are hosted in the United States. If you access the Site or Services from any other region, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, or Services, you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States and, where the laws of your country allow you to do so, you consent to that transfer and authorize us to store and use your data in the United States. Additionally, you understand that your Personal Information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing Personal Information are different, and potentially less stringent, than in your country. 

We participate in the EU-U.S. and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce to ensure an adequate level of protection for certain Personal Information received on the Site in the U.S. from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Please see our Privacy Shield Policy at <https://www.prolificworks.com/about/privacyshield> for information about Libboo's data practices regarding Personal Information it receives from European Union member countries and Switzerland pursuant to the respective Privacy Shield frameworks. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program generally, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. If you have a Privacy Shield-related complaint, please contact us at [support@prolificworks.com](mailto:support@prolificworks.com). 

###  Sharing your personal information 

We do not knowingly share, sell, trade, or rent Users' Personal Information to others, except as described in this Privacy Policy or on the Site. For example, we may share Personal Information as follows: 

  * in aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted subsidiaries and affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above; 

  * with service providers (" **Service Providers** ") such as contractors, vendors and consultants who work with us for the operation of the Site or other service we offer and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us (subject to obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and other appropriate confidentiality and security measures); 

  * when a User gives consent to do so including, and not limited to, if we notify a User through the Site that the information provided will be shared in a manner and a User provides such information; 

  * when we are lawfully authorized or required to do so, or we believe in good faith that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants, or court orders; 

  * to enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Terms and Conditions, or our other policies or agreements 

  * if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Libboo, Inc.our customers or others; and 

  * relating to, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where Personal Information may be disclosed or transferred as one of the business assets of Libboo, Inc. 

We may also share the information we have collected when a User agrees to receive information from third parties (e.g., by choosing to "opt-in" to such communications). If a User is presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers from one or more third parties, and consents to receiving such information, Prolific Works is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, a User should review those privacy policies and practices prior to agreeing to share their Personal Information. If the User later decides that they no longer want to receive communication from a third party, they will need to contact that third party directly. Nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregated or anonymized information, which may be shared with third parties without User consent. 

Our Site, Prolific Works content sharing platform, and Services contain links to, and allow you to share content on, third party websites and services. The fact that we link to a website or service or allow you to share content on them is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. This privacy policy applies only as provided in the scope section above. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

###  Managing your personal information with us 

You control the personal data you share with us and you can access or rectify this data at any time. If you have registered an account on Prolific Works, you can submit a request to [support@prolificworks.com](mailto:support@prolificworks.com) to access, correct, delete, or modify the personal data you provided to us and associated with your account. We also provide you the opportunity to object, restrict or withdraw consent where applicable for the use of data you have provided to us by submitting a request to [support@prolificworks.com](mailto:support@prolificworks.com). We will export the data you shared through our services to a third party at any time upon your request. You can also cancel your account by submitting a request to [support@prolificworks.com](mailto:support@prolificworks.com). We generally delete closed account information within 90 days of account closure, except that we do retain your personal data if reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, and prevent fraud and abuse. We will retain de-personalized information after your account has been closed. 

We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have lawful bases. Lawful bases include consent (where you have given consent), contract (where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you), and "legitimate interests". Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time and where we rely on legitimate interests, you have the right to object. 

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Libboo has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the Personal Information we collect. Your continued use of the Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

###  Your acceptance of these terms 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding our information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy, our [Community Guidelines](https://www.prolificworks.com/about/communityguidelines) and [Terms of Service](https://www.prolificworks.com/about/terms). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

###  Contacting us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: 

Prolific Works c/o Libboo  
9 Munroe Avenue  
Watertown, MA 02472  

__ Back to About
